desimad.com 2012-09-20

# Desimad | Privacy Policy

**We at IDream Holdings Pvt. Ltd..... ( herein IDream Holdings) recognize the importance of protecting your personal and other information which we regard to be personal to you.**

 **IDream Holdings** as a provider of the services of the website DESIMAD which is an interactive and entertainment site having several features, activities and contests which require the exchange of prizes, goods and services and hence it becomes necessary for us at IDream Holdings to obtain personal information about you. This information assists us in serving and identifying you better. We know you may be concerned about what we do with the personal information provided by you hence below is the important information related to the protection and confidentiality of your personal and other information. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us at [contact@desimad.in](mailto:contact@desimad.in)

You have our assurance that: 

· We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. 

· We only use your personal information to help us service your better and/or improve the services being provided by us and be able to identify you at any given point in time especially when the time comes to give away prizes and awards. 

· We do not sell your personal information to third parties. We do, however, share selected information under certain conditions: (1) We may share information as part of normal business operations and as part of normal legal/regulatory purposes required by the Law in India and/or any other regulatory and government entities; and (2) We may occasionally invite selected third parties to participate in offers we feel would be attractive to you as a licensed registered user of the website DESIMAD.(3) We may utilize the personal information submitted by you for data collection, assessment of feedback, your views but we do not in any manner identify you in person. 

· We protect your account information by placing it on the secure portion of our Web site. That's why you have to enter a unique User Name and Password each time you want to access your account information. In addition, you can use the Log Off button located throughout the site to securely exit your account without closing your browser. Your Password should never be shared with anyone. Your Password with the DESIMAD website is a password that only you know. It should never be shared with anyone and should be changed frequently. You can change your password anytime after logging on to the Customer Center . 

· The DESIMAD Website does not collect personally identifying information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide tailored information from a Website. A cookie is an element of data that a Website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. IDream Holdings only offers cookies to licensed registered users so they do not have to go through the process of re-entering their User Names and Passwords each time they want to access the members-only areas of the DESIMAD Website. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. 

· The DESIMAD Website contains links to other Websites. IDream Holdings is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

· We at IDream Holdings have taken all efforts and pains to maintain and control the non disclosure and illegitimate use of your personal information provided to us. However inspite of all our efforts in securing and preventing the unwanted use and/or disclosure of your personal information there always exists a possibility that there may be an illegal and unwarranted access of your personal information by others. Should you learn about such illegal use of your personal information then please contact us at [contact@desimad.in](mailto:contact@desimad.in)

· Cookies 

"Cookies" are data files sent by a Web site to your computer memory. They can be used to track activity on the site and help protect the security of confidential data. 

Your privacy and security are not compromised when you accept a cookie from our Web site -- no other company can access DESIMAD cookie information except IDream Holdings. In addition, cookies from a secure site such as DESIMAD are encrypted and sent securely. The information stored in the cookie is only valid for a single session, and would be useless after you log out even if someone could decipher it. For more information, read how cookies enhance Web site performance. 

· E-mail at [contact@desimad.in](mailto:contact@desimad.in)

E-mail is an important communication channel. On occasions, we may use your e-mail address to send you communications with information about contests, services and/or products that we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such unsolicited communications from IDream Holdings , simply contact us at [contact@desimad.in](mailto:contact@desimad.in)

· Ensuring your information is correct 

If for any reason you are concerned that the personal or account information maintained with IDream Holdings is not correct, please contact us at [contact@desimad.in](mailto:contact@desimad.in)
